Why him, of all people?
What was Father thinking?
Giving a man of unknown
lineage the Black Blade?
It was from back when
Father was an adventurer.
He and the Sovereign
Six had pushed deep into
the darkest corner of
the Dungeon of the Lost.
It was a long and dangerous quest that,
upon exiting, yielded a prime dungeon relic.
That Blade is the most powerful.
Made of an unknown material
harder than mithril
or a calcum or even
monometal no matter the
technique or skill used
nothing can cause even
a scratch upon it it
has become known as the
unbreakable blade the
biggest question is given
its resilience how could
such an indestructible
material gotten so
beaten up that sword has
value beyond that of a
weapon how could he just?
let such a thing go.
No, I'm thinking about this wrong.
Father has also noticed the sense of
unrest hanging over the country.
In all likelihood, he is
putting his faith in that man.
The one who defeated a rampaging
minotaur and saved Lin's life.
He might very well be
our secret weapon for
whatever is sure to happen in the future.
Oh, wait, Lynn.
Can you be seen out here in public? Yes.
First and foremost, I am an adventurer.
Um, well, okay.
I'm thinking we should go
to the guild after we eat.
That sounds terrific, instructor.
Oh, man.
I'm really not the type
of guy who should be
considered capable enough
of instructing Anybody?
Anything?
How did everything get so complicated
and she just follows me around
everywhere all the time?
Once I get some real work from the guild,
she'll finally be able to
grasp how clueless I am
out there and drop this
whole instructor nonsense?
I hope that you can find.
a befitting task soon, Instructor!
Let's eat!
For every moment, the truth is not
allowed to be able to afford anything.
What can I have for you?
I can't take it away from my heart,
but I will never be able to get back.
Even if it is a dream,
I'm not allowed to go back.
I'm not allowed to be able to get it.
Thank you so much for watching.
Noor, why are you here
with Lady Lindbergh?
Master! Huh?
As an adventurer, I go by the name Lin.
No need to add any titles.
Uh, okay.
My apologies, Lin.
Hey, what's all this, Noor?
Did anything else happen to you yesterday?
Oh, well, uh, it's kind of
difficult to explain. Hmm?
Well, one of our rules is not sticking
your nose where it doesn't belong.
Forget I asked.
Oh, I was hoping he'd give me some advice.
So, what brings you in today?
Looking for work?
Oh, uh, yeah.
One that two people can do, if possible.
A two-person job, huh? Hmm.
So if I remember correctly,
you're Silver B-Ring, right? Yes!
If you two form a party together, you
can take on the goblin hunting job?
in the outskirts of the capital.
Oh, man!
A goblin hunting job?
Goblins are the monsters
that adventurers all over
the world fight to put
their skills to the test.
Wait, sir, can we really take
on an adventure like that? Yeah.
Lynn can accept silver tasks
like this all on her own,
but bringing along a partner like you?
with a lower rank than
hers is a big liability.
Normally, the job will drop
down a rank or two, though.
I don't believe this! A quest!
Outside the castle!
Whoa, hold it.
This means I'm completely taking
advantage of Lin's adventurer rank.
And let's be real.
Up until now, all I've wanted
is for her to go back home.
She sees right through me.
I'm such a scumbag, and she knows it.
Even so, she does still want to be here.
All the time.
Um, what's wrong, Instructor?
Well, yeah.
Sure you're okay with this?
I mean, as it is,
I'm relying solely on your rank to
take on this goblin hunting job.
Of course I'm okay with it!
If there's anything I can do for
you, just say the word, alright?
Oh, seriously?
Yes, I do feel kind of bad for
using her status to get ahead.
But hey, one of my lifelong
dreams is finally coming true!
Alright, we're heading out!
Wait, I haven't told you where
you're going or anything.
Oh, yeah, right.
But you want to take it anyway, don't you?
Well, of course.
Now don't go nuts out there.
A low threat level doesn't mean that
it's easy peasy, okay? Don't you worry.
I'm well aware of my limitations.
You're going to this area here.
Only report what you catch.
That's the Forest of Beast. Correct.
The right ear will be the
proof of your success.
You won't be getting paid without it.
So be sure to bring it back. Understood.
Bring back the right ear.
So there have been reports of their
numbers diminishing quite a bit lately.
If you don't come across one, then go
ahead and pick some medicinal herbs.
Right.
Now go on, get on with it.
And I'm serious, don't get hurt.
And here we go.
Open the gate!
Adventure onward! Right! Sure thing!
So we are in the Forest of the Beasts.
The trees are getting
pretty dense, aren't they?
These are different types of plants than
what we see in the southern forests.
They're gargantuan.
The ecological system here is very unique.
Yeah, you're not kidding.
Lynn, what kind of
creatures are goblins? What?
I mean, I'd like to at least
hear about them beforehand. Sure.
Normally they hunt small animals as prey?
And eat the fruits off trees,
but they've been attacking
humans for sustenance lately.
If we leave them be,
their numbers grow too large which leads
to a food shortage which in turn would
overflow into human villages.
That's why adventurers
are regularly dispatched
to hunt them and control their numbers.
Control them?
The health of the ecological
system of the forest
actually depends on
whether or not there are
goblins, which means we don't want
to hunt them to extinction either.
Also, this forest has rare flora and
fauna that are not found in other places,
so it's Sometimes used for training,
for beginner adventurers
to forage and hunt.
Good to know.
Not only does Lynn have the skills,
she knows all sorts of... stuff.
What can I possibly teach this person?
You got anything?
Afraid not? None here? Either?
That's strange. Right?
Under normal circumstances, we would
have encountered a few of them already.
I suppose the rumors
about the goblin numbers.
dwindling are true.
I'm getting something from
a creature to the northwest.
I'll pinpoint its location.
So we found one? Yes.
It shouldn't take too
much time to get there.
Let's go take a look.
It keeps getting darker and darker.
There are some extremely
old trees in this area.
Makes it hard for the
sun to shine through.
Goblins are known to
prefer a place like this.
Of course they would.
Huh?
What's wrong?
The presence of a monster was right
up ahead, but all of a sudden...
It disappeared.
It's gone? Yes.
Monsters are living beings like us, right?
So you think that they can maybe
just die from illness or old age?
Um, yeah, I guess that
could be a possibility.
It was around here!
I don't see anything.
Yeah, me neither.
No, wait. Hold on.
What is that?
Uncover!
Wait, what is that?
It's a goblin.
A big one, too.
So that's a goblin?
It's way bigger than I imagined.
They're said to be one of the weakest,
but there's a huge difference in hearing
about it and meeting one face to face.
The gnarly beast has all
the calling cards green
skin walking on two legs
piercing glowing eyes.
And they use tools.
I'll bet all you higher ranked adventurers
handle these guys like they're nothing.
Huh?
Okay.
So she's freaked out.
She may be blessed with abilities but...
She has very little
actual combat experience.
You don't need to be frightened.
We're only up against a goblin.
Terrifying, but worry about that later.
We got this.
Right, let's go!
I'm covered!
This is...
it can't be...
No, it's the Goblin Emperor.
A subspecies of the Goblin King,
considered an extreme threat.
The Goblin Emperor is a beast created
from genetic manipulation by mankind.
In fact,
the deviant research that brought forth
this forbidden knowledge is now banned.
On top of that, this
one eats its own kind,
ingesting their power and
growing even stronger.
You don't need to be frightened.
We're only up against a goblin.
Wait a minute.
Did Nor come here because of this goblin?
He was so excited to take
on this job because he
wanted to eliminate a threat
no one else knew about.
I've got your back, Lin.
That's right.
I am not alone.
Right!
Let's go!
Perry!
Trying to corner me?
Nah, I ain't gonna let that happen.
Lynn! On it!
Full windcutter!
Icicle dance!
I can't hit him!
I didn't think it could be so quick!
Perry!
Instructor!
Are you alright?
Look out!
Perry! Perry!
I have to do something!
Huh?
Hang on.
Where's the wound?
Goblin emperors shouldn't be
able to recover so easily.
That's it! Instructor!
The stone on its forehead!
If you can get that off, we can defeat it!
No way!
He was watching how many I could handle.
I can't block them all.
Windblast!
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I knew it.
It's constantly replenishing
its power with the monostone.
If we keep fighting like this, we're going
to run out of both stamina and magic.
But if your magic attacks aren't
able to hit them and keep them down,
nothing I can do is going to work.
Hey, Lin.
Can you aim that attack at my back?
Wait, what?
You mean windblast? Yeah.
That move is powerful enough
to demolish Castle Balls.
You don't possibly want me to...
I think I'll be okay.
I have this to protect me.
Our only chance of getting
out of here is to be faster.
Okay.
Here we go. Let her rip.
Full weight loss. Fast!
Physical enhancement.
Feather steps.
Low heel.
Instructor!
Where's the stone?
It's right here.
Lynn, can you be the one to finish it off?
And please don't let it suffer
any more than it already has.
Yes, of course I can.
Hellfire!
I'm sorry, goblin.
I think I'll refrain from any more
goblin slaying for the time being.
I was way overconfident and got
into too many dangerous situations.
I'll have to do a lot more training
before taking on the next challenge.
So it was a goblin emperor, huh?
It must have been quite powerful.
With this size monostone,
it's larger than normal.
According to the reports, it was
several times the size of a goblin king.
I'm sure it was.
The size is unusual.
The Magic Empire may be
responsible for the event itself.
But still, this stone, though.
We think, sir, it could be a demon's
heart from the holy theocracy of Mithra.
How is Lin?
Only minor wounds.
It must have been a terribly hard battle.
It's amazing they were able to survive.
The monster itself hid
behind a powerful seal
and ambushed them in the forest of beasts.
The lady believes it had
been there a few days,
and in fact, maybe even
more than that. A few days?
So this seal is one that not even
the secret core can perceive.
But how are they transporting such a bulky
thing all the way here in the first place?
If they use summoning magic,
the sensory network in the
capital should have caught it.
Did nothing show up in the perimeter?
The number of goblins was decreasing,
so the Adventurer's Guild
requested an investigation into it.
There may have been several similar
cases in other areas as well.
This report is a summary of questionable
instances from the last three months.
Well done, gentlemen.
Continue with the inquiry.
Well, look at you.
I never thought that the little runt from
way back when would
grow up to slay goblins?
It was so much nastier
that I thought it would be.
But Lynn came in at the last moment and we
managed to get the job done. No problem.
Oh, no, that's not how it went
It happened my very first
hunt I should celebrate
it may be just another
quest to other adventurers.
But to me this is you know
everything you did well?
Best to just watch from the
sidelines and let her handle it.
And I guess probably it's
the wiser choice, too, eh?
You know what?
I'm just grateful I got to
help her out a little bit.
I have no idea where I'd be
if Lynn hadn't been there.
But I'm the one that just
helped you out, remember?
Well, even goblins can still be a
threat to newbies from time to time.
But it was a good
experience for you, right?
Exactly, it certainly was.
Until I saw one in real life, I had no
idea goblins were anything like that.
And who knew about the stone on
its forehead being a weak point?
A stone on the forehead?
What are you talking about?
Yeah, kind of a shiny reddish color.
And kind of pretty, actually.
Oh, you mean a monostone.
It's normally buried in
the heart or the throat.
Hmm.
Are you sure that was
really a goblin, my boy?
Yeah, well, of course.
A goblin, right? Indeed.
If that's what you say it is, instructor,
then that is that, no
matter what anybody says.
Might have been a rare type, I guess.
All right, let's see
the proof of the kill.
I'm going to get your cash.
The right ear?
I told you to bring back the right ear?
No way.
Um, we might have set that goblin on fire.
You did what?
Oh?
Oh!